在这个视频中，我们将把前面几个视频中学到的所有知识整合在一起，创建
In this video, we'll put together everything we've learned in the previous videos to create
一个端到端的客户服务助手示例。
an end-to-end example of a customer service assistant.
我们将执行以下步骤：
We'll go through the following steps.
首先，我们会检查输入内容，看是否触发了内容审核 API。
First, we'll check the input to see if it flags the moderation API.
其次，如果没有，我们将提取产品列表。
Second, if it doesn't, we'll extract the list of products.
第三，如果找到了产品，我们会尝试查找它们。
Third, if the products are found, we'll try to look them up.
第四，我们将用模型回答用户的问题。
And four, we'll answer the user question with the model.
最后，我们会将答案通过内容审核 API检查。
And finally, we'll put the answer through the moderation API.
如果没有被标记有问题，我们会将答案返回给用户。
And if it is not flagged, we'll return it to the user.
我们已经有了相关设置。
So we have our setup.
这里新增了一个额外的引用。
We have this additional import.
这是一个用于聊天机器人界面的Python包。
This is a Python package we'll use for a chatbot UI.
我要粘贴一个处理用户消息的函数。
And so I'm going to paste in a function process_user_message.
实际上，我先运行一个例子，然后我们再讨论这个函数。
And I'm actually going to run an example first, and then we'll talk through the function.
这是一段我们一直在使用的用户输入：
So we have our user input that we've been using.
“告诉我关于SmartX pro手机和相机的信息。
Tell me about the SmartX pro phone and the camera.
还告诉我关于电视的信息。”
Also tell me about TVs.
那我们来运行这个。
So let's run this.
首先，我们来运行这个。
First, let's run this.
正如你所看到的，我们正在通过这些步骤来回答用户的问题。
So as you can see, we're going through the steps to answer the user question.
第一步是审核步骤。
So the first step, the moderation step.
第二步是提取产品列表。
The second step is extracting the list of products.
第三步是查找产品信息。
The third step is looking up the product information.
现在有了这些产品信息，模型正试图回答这个问题，
And so now with this product information, the model is trying to answer the question,
正如我们在之前的视频中看到的。
as we've seen in the previous videos.
最后，它再次通过审核API处理返回结果，以确保对用户展示的内容是安全的。
And then finally, it puts the response through the moderation API again to make sure it's safe to show to the user.
这就是我们现在熟悉的返回结果。
And so this is the response that we're now familiar with.
让我们浏览一下代码看这里发生了什么。
And so let's talk through a little bit of what's happening.
有一个辅助函数process_user_message。
So we have our helper function process_user_message.
它接收用户输入，即当前消息，以及到目前为止的所有消息数组。
Takes in the user input, which is the current message, and an array of all of the messages so far.
这就是我们构建聊天机器人界面的时候。
And this is when we build the chatbot UI.
首先，检查输入是否触发了审查API。
So the first step, checking to see if the input flags the moderation API.
我们在之前的视频中讲过这个。
We covered this in a previous video.
如果输入被标记，那么告诉用户我们无法处理这个请求。
If the input is flagged, then we tell the user that we can't process the request.
如果没有被标记，尝试提取产品列表，就像在之前的视频中那样。
If it is not flagged, we try to extract the list of products, as we did in the previous video.
然后尝试查找产品。
Then we try to look up the products.
在这种情况下，如果没有找到产品，这将只是一个空字符串。
And in this case, if no products are found, this will just be an empty string.
然后我们回答用户的问题。
Then we answer the user question.
我们提供了对话历史和带有相关产品信息的新消息。
So we give the conversation history and the new messages with the relevant product information.
我们得到了返回结果。
So we get the response.
然后我们将这个返回结果通过审核 API检查。
And then we run this response through the moderation API.
如果被标记，我们会告诉用户我们无法提供这个信息。
If it's flagged, we tell the user that we can't provide this information.
也许我们会说一些类似，“让我帮你转接人工服务。”
Maybe we'll say something, "Let me connect you to a human."
然后你可以采取一些后续步骤。
And you could take some subsequent step.
让我们用一个漂亮的界面把这些都整合起来，试着进行一次对话。
And so let's put this all together with a nice UI and try to have a conversation.
这里有一个功能，只要我们与助手互动，这些消息就会被累积起来。
So here we have a function that will just accumulate the messages as we interact with the assistant.
请随时暂停视频，以更详细地了解这是如何工作的。
And feel free to pause the video to understand in more detail how this works.
当然，对刚才非常长的处理用户消息功能的那部分，您也可以一样随时暂停去详细了解。
And of course, feel free to do the same for the really long process user message function that we just saw as well.
现在我们要粘贴代码来显示聊天机器人界面。
So now we're going to paste in our code to display the chatbot UI.
那么，如果我们运行这个，现在让我们尝试和客服助手进行对话。
So if we run this, now let's try and have a conversation with the customer service assistant.
那我们问一下：“你们有哪些电视？”
So let's ask, "What TVs do you have?"
在后台，助手正在执行处理用户消息功能中的所有步骤。
And under the hood, the assistant is going through all of the steps in the process user message function.
它列出了各种不同的电视。
So it's listed a variety of different TVs.
现在我们再问：“哪个最便宜？”
So now let's ask, "Which is the cheapest?"
同样，它还在执行所有相同的步骤，但这次它还将历史会话一起传递到Prompt中。
Again, it's going through all the same steps, but this time it's passing the conversation history as well into the prompts.
好的，它告诉我们这个扬声器是我们拥有的最便宜的与电视相关的产品。
Okay, so it's telling us that this speaker is the cheapest TV-related product we have.
有意思。
Interesting.
我们看看最贵的是什么。
Let's see what the most expensive is.
最贵的电视是 Cineview 8K 电视。
So the most expensive TV is the Cineview 8K TV.
那我们来了解更多关于它的信息吧。
So let's ask for more information about it.
跟我说说更多关于它的事。
Tell me more about it.
我们收到了关于这台电视的更多信息。
And so we've received some more information about this television.
在这个例子中，我们将在课程中学到的技巧结合起来，创建了
So in this example, we've combined the techniques we've learned throughout the course to create
一个包含一系列步骤的综合系统，用于评估用户输入、处理它们，
a comprehensive system with a chain of steps that evaluates user inputs, processes them,
然后检查输出。
and then checks the output.
通过监控更多输入的系统质量，
By monitoring the quality of the system across a larger number of inputs,
你可以改变步骤，提高系统的整体性能。
you can alter the steps and improve the overall performance of your system.
也许会发现我们的Prompt在某些步骤上可以做得更好。
Maybe we might find that our prompts could be better for some of the steps.
也许有些步骤甚至不需要。
Maybe some of the steps aren't even necessary.
你会找到更好的检索方法，等等。
You will find a better retrieval method, and so on.
我们将在下一个视频中进一步讨论这个问题。
We'll discuss this more in the next video.